The Call of the Wild is a action, adventure, drama film directed by Ken Annakin.
John Thornton, is a fearless man who's after more
than gold; he wants to do what's right.
Thornton works for the U.S.
mail and is the only person daring and smart enough to figure out how to travel the
deadly 600 miles from Skagway to Dawson, Alaska in the icy winter.
His incredibly dog Buck is by his side and part of how he survives.
John Thornton, played by Charlton Heston.
Pete, played by Raimund Harmstorf.
Black Burton, played by George Eastman.
Mercedes, played by Maria Rohm.
Seze, played by Juan Luis Galiardo.
Taglish Charlie, played by Sancho Gracia.
The Call of the Wild is a 1972 family adventure film directed by Ken Annakin and starring
Charlton Heston, Michèle Mercier, Raimund Harmstorf, George Eastman, and Maria Rohm.
It was written by Peter Yeldham, Peter Welbeck and Wyn Wells based on Jack London's 1903 novel The Call of the Wild,
the film follows the adventures of Buck, a dog that is brought north to Canada to be used as a sled dog.
The tone is emotional.